Guide to the Mark Bloch Postal Art Network (PAN) Archive MSS.170
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Mail Art and Correspondence, 1976-2009; 22.5 Linear Feet in 44 manuscript boxes, 8 box binders, and 6 oversize flat boxes.
  - Spain, 1983-2003 (Box 10, Folder 17-18, Box 11, Folder 1-2, Box 86, Folder 5,7,8, Box 90, Box 95, Folder 6, Box 103, Folder 11)
    Correspondents include: 10.000 Humans Edicions, 4 Sellos, Alena Laufrova, Antonio Gomez, Boek, Centro Cívico Social, César Reglero Campos, Eduard Escofet, EL OLIVARe, Facultad de Bellas Artes (Cuenca, Spain), Fernando Matamoros, Francesco Vidal, Hilda Fuchs, Ibirico, Isabel Jover, JBB (Magico Verdun), Joan Borda i Boreu, Jordi Solé, José Antonio Sarmiento, José Maria Beneitez, Josean M.L., Juan Manuel Alvarez Cebrián, Juan Manuel Ruiz Solsona, Julio Sánchez Oliver, Koine, Pedro Bericat, Pere Sousa, Pilar Varela, Poisson Soluble Gallery, Radio Nacional de España, Rafael Flores, Rafael Ventín, Sissokou Mamadou, Spanish Mail Art Association, Western Sahara, Xoan Anleo.
  - Sweden, 1983-1998 (Box 11, Folder 3-6, Box 85, Folder 6, Box 94, Folder 8, Box 96, Folder 5, Box 98, Box 99, Box 103, Folder 12)
    Correspondents include: Jaromir Svozilik, Joachim Bursell, Kajco Design, Kjell Nyman, Leif Eriksson, Mark Horner, Marten Lindbcom, Maryanne Hagnosson, Peter Ahlberg, Peter Meyer, Target Media, Uddah-Buddah.
  - Switzerland, 1983-1995 (Box 11, Folder 7-10, Box 87, Folder 5, Box 89, Box 91, Folder 4, Box 98, Box 99, Box 103, Folder 13)
    Correspondents include: Calypso Now, Christoph Oberholzer, Claudia Schmidt, Copy-Left (Manfred Stirnemann), Dao Badao Publishers, Günther Ruch, Hans Ruedi Fricker, Jacqueline Niwel, Jean-Marc Rastorfer, Marcel Stüssi.
  - Thailand, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Correspondents include: Byron Black
  - Unidentified Countries, 1983-1990 (Box 83, Folder 8-9, Box 84, Folder 3, Box 97, Flat-file-folder 6 Right, Flat-file-folder 9, Box 105, Folder 4, Box 104, Folder 2)
    Correspondents include: Aaron Kline, Aleksey Kurchuk, Jaymz Schemer, Judy Gorman, Phil Nurenberg, Sophia Martinou, The Postal Art Network Children's Art On The Theme "One World"..
  - United Kingdom, 1983-2001 (Box 11, Folder 13, Box 12, Folder 1-7, Box 83, Folder 3, Box 85, Folder 5, Box 86, Folder 1,8, Box 87, Folder 4, Binder 16, Binder 17, Box 88, Box 90, Box 94, Folder 9, Box 98, Box 104, Folder 1)
    Correspondents include: A1 Waste Paper Co., Ade Barradel/Allison Lloyd, B.E Pilcher, Barry Pitcher, Ben Allen, Boyle Family, C.Nile Magazine, Dawn Redwood, Diane Dixon, DJ Bell, E.f., Eric Finlay, Erica van Hora, Feeding Squirrels to Nuts, Frank Smith, Hazel, I.S.A.B.N, International Review of Printing and Publishing, Intl Biography Center, Jeruen Teunen, John Furnival, M.A Longbottom, Mark Pawson, Michael Lumb, Murray, O. Jason (The Institute of Fatuous Research), Paul Tucker, Pete Horobin, RER Megacorp, Robin Crozier, Roger Cleghorn, Routine Art, S. Hone, Snowhite Young, Stefan Szczelkun, Torquil Anderson, Wall Magazine, Working Press.
  - United States (Alabama), 1979-1989 (Box 12, Folder 8, Box 88, Box 99, Box 104, Folder 3)
    Correspondents include: Jackie Olson, Unknown Arkansas (New York Correspondence School).
  - United States (Alaska), 1986-1994 (Box 12, Folder 9, Box 88, Box 93, Folder 3)
    Correspondents include: Leslie, The Artic Roadrunners (Jim and Marsha Anne).
  - United States (Arizona), 1984-2009 (Box 12, Folder 10, Box 13, Folder 1, Box 85, Folder 5, Box 87, Folder 2, Binder 17, Box 88, Box 89, Box 90, Box 94, Box 98, Box 100, Folder 3, Box 104, Folder 4)
    Correspondents include: Amy M. Bowling, Arthur Secunda, Carol Stetser, Cynthia Stillzoe, Cynthia Thompson, Florentin Smarandache, John Tonemah, Johnny Barnard, Kristin Geihl, Pedro Pescador, Peter Rassa (Metrophobia), Plutonium Press, Ron Gasowski, University of Phoenix.
  - United States (Arkansas), 2003-2005 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Correspondents include: buzZ blurr
  - United States (California), 1978-2006 (Box 13, Folder 3-9, Box 14, Folder 1-13, Box 18, Folder 1-8, Box 19, Folder 1-7, Box 20, Folder 1, Box 83, Folder 3,5, Box 84, Folder 1,2,5, Box 85, Box 86, Folder 1,2,3,6,8, Box 87, Folder 1-5, Binder 15, Binder 16, Binder 17, Box 88, Box 89, Box 90, Box 91, Folder 2022-05-06T00:00:00+00:00, Box 92, Folder 2, Box 95, Folder 2022-07-08T00:00:00+00:00, Box 98, Box 99, Box 104, Folder 5)
    Correspondents include: AARDVARK, Abracadada, Achim Snyder, Aerosol, Age of Consent, Alien and Shaver, Alien Communications, Allison, Alta Bradford, AMK (Banned Productions), Amnesia (Monica Rex), Anonymous (Oakland), Anonymous (Van Nuys, California), Art Hopkins, Art Issues, Art Radio, Arturo Fallico, Astro Artz, Banned Productions, Barry Berg, Barry Ziff, Beverly Innsteep, Bill Gaglione, Bill Hardin, Box of Water, Brenda Kays, C.Z. Lovecraft, Carl Andre, Carla Cryptic, Carol Poundstone, Cellini, Charles Goldstein, Cherry and Mike Leslie, Chief Crazy Glue, Chubb, Chud Co, Collector's Choice Gallery, Contagion, Contemporary Art Press, Craig Hill, CSC-San Bernardino Art Department, CSUN/USU, Dale Johnson, Darlene Altschul, David Hunter, David Kephart, David Zack, Dawn Domini, Denis Fudsworth, Denver Tuscon, Dierdre Feehan, DKA, Douglas L. Marsh, Dr. Jampf, Dwyer Family, Eat Art (Mike Dyar), Eat it up, Edith Abeyta, Endangered Species, Fast Cheap and Easy Graphics, Feehan, Fluxus Penpal Network, Framework, Full Gallop, G. Arthur Hopkins, Gene Lawson, Gerlovins (L.A. Contemporary Exhibitions), Ginny Lloyd, Goethe Institute, Group Coca-Cola, Guzbro Tapes, Hardbound Ed, Harley (Terra Candella), Heaton, Heavy Shades, Her, Hermine Stover (Endangered Species), High Performance, Horseman, Human House, Ilene Goldstein, Infekt Gruppe, Information Sickness, Information Sickness (Alan K. Lipton), Irvine Fine Arts Center, Isla van Hook, Janea Moksness, Janet Ziff, JED, Jeff Kurvnik, Jeff Mullicon, Jesse Edwards, Jim Martin (Flatland), Jim Reva, Joan Eppich, John A. Mozzer, John Tostado, Johnny B, Johnny Brewton, Jon Mardian, Judith Hoffberg, Judy Kleinberg, Karen Holden, Karen Politovich, Kathy Chambers, Kathy Johnson, Ken Klinkert (The Skipper), Kim, LA Obscurist Society, LAICA, Larry P.Mullins, Leavenworth Jackson, Leon Herbst, Michael Lipman (Lip), Little Lulu, Lon Spiegelman, Lori, M. Stevens, M.Kline, Madame X, Marc Herbert, Mark Hurlstone, Maura Framson, Maureen Steve Malloy, Metro, Michael Mollet, Michael "Squid Digger" Lund, Mike Bishop (California State University), Mike Dyar, Mike Schoenberg, Minoy, Mishka, Mng, Monica Rex, More O'Malloy, Morton Klein, Naomi Ramieri-Hall, Nikki and Jud Schwartz, No Business As Usual Action Network, Norman Solomon, Nothing Much Productions, Occupant, Ocean Drive, Opal Molety, Opal Nations, Outdoor TV (Video Congress), Pamela Balanag, Pango Pango, Pat Lay Wilson, Patrickt, Patty Nation, Paul Forte, Penelope Dwyer, Perry Lenhart, Philip R. Nurenberg, PIX (Pat Wilson), Pix Susan C., Postal Commemorative Society, Postal Flow West, Private World, Rachel Carpenter, Rachel Rosenthal, Radio Free Dada, Radio Mambo, Randy Kopang, Rich Evac, Richard Bloch, Richard Meade, Rob Cummings, Rocola (Marlon Vito Picasso), Rogue's Gallery, Rubber Stamp Exchange (Bill Gaglione), Rudolph, Ruggero Magi, Ruth Howard, Scott Hecker, Scroti, SDSU, Sherri Houser, Sonja van der Burg, Sprout, Stamp Art Gallery, Stephen Olsay, Stephen Perkins, Steve C. Bothers, Steve Malloy, Steve Mcdonald, Steve Sikora, Susan Shaw, Suzie Sachs, T G Ross, T. Heiney, Takayo, Target LA, Terry Gross, The Duke, The Fault, The Fire House Volunteer Muster Roll, The Joke Project (Toshi Onuki), The Soft Touch, Tony Kennedy, Trash and Treasure, Turk le Claire, Tyler James Hoare, Typo Press, U'MOMA (Buster Cleveland), Ursula Peters, Vermont Street Week, Vicki and Greg van Hook, Vicki Armstrong, Vicki van Hook, Victor Perez, Victoria Kelly, Visual Response League (Alan H. Nakagawa), Zoe Goldman, ZTZSU.
  - United States (Colorado), 1983-1994 (Box 20, Folder 2-3, Box 84, Folder 4, Box 85, Folder 1,3, Binder 17, Box 89, Box 90, Box 92, Folder 3, Box 98, Box 99)
    Correspondents include: Clare Forster, Durango Fire Artists Council, E.G.G., Harry Bates Club, Ileen Bloch, James Prez, Kathy Rolenz, Pamela Chaddic, SAWN, T. Wakabayashi, Teresink Pereria.
  - United States (Connecticut), 1982-1995 (Box 20, Folder 4-5, Binder 17, Box 89, Box 100, Folder 1-2)
    Correspondents include: D.S Boenhart, Elliot Books, Institute of Children's Literature, Joan Coderre, Postal Commemorative Society, Premises, Rosebud Matchbox Art Museum, T. Sikorski, Taunton Press.
  - United States (Florida), 1981-2004 (Box 20, Folder 6-10, Box 48, Folder 1, Box 84, Folder 2,4, Box 86, Folder 3, Box 87, Binder 17, Box 88, Box 90, Box 92, Folder 4, Box 93, Box 97, Box 98, Box 99, Box 104, Folder 6)
    Correspondents include: Boon Dance Baby Pants, Contender, Doo Da Florida, E. Mela, Emo Chanel, Epistolary Stud Farm, Evil Genius, F.C. Jerkoffski, FSU Four Arts, Harry Fox, Jack Saunders, Kasher Communications, Kenneth Karsten, Lee Taylor, Nicholas Bergery, Patti Taylor, Post-Industrialism, Ryan, Small Publishers Co-Op, Steve Bradely, Sullama, Tampon Springs Recreation Department, The Church of Christ (Michael Voodoo), Thunderstruck, Tick Tock Tick Tock, Tommy Mew.
  - United States (Georgia), 1982-2005 (Box 48, Folder 2-4, Box 84, Folder 4, Box 85, Folder 5, Box 86, Folder 2,8, Box 87, Folder 3, Binder 16, Box 88, Box 91, Folder 7, Box 92, Box 94, Folder 11, Box 98)
    Correspondents include: Akoma Beaman, Art Papers, Art Posto, Baseball Ink, Bill Chambers, Boon Dance Baby Pants, Buzzard Cult, Epistolary Stud Farm, Gordon Jr. College, Ileen Bloch, Jack Saunders, Jack Sinclair, John Thomas, Rubberwoman, Shelby Publishing Co, Inc., Theresa Walker.
  - United States (Hawaii), 1995 (Box 48, Folder 5, Box 83, Box 86, Folder 1, Box 88)
    Correspondents include: EROTICA
  - United States (Idaho), 1989-1993 (Box 48, Folder 6, Box 99)
    Correspondents include: Coldwater Creek, Larry Mullins.
  - United States (Illinois), 1983-1995 (Box 48, Folder 7-8, Box 84, Folder 2, Box 86, Folder 1, Binder 15, Binder 17, Box 88, Box 89, Box 90, Box 98, Box 99, Box 104, Folder 7)
    Correspondents include: Artists Book Works, Artists Call, Arto Posto, Ashley Parker Owens, Axe St. Arena, Bonnie Sohn, Brendan de Vallance, Carroll Brooks, Correspondence Art Club, El Archivero, Karen Dean, Ken Thompson (P-Form), Mantra Mash, Michelle F, MR Bop, Ms. K, N.A.M.E. Gallery, Spike, The Crazy Camel.
  - United States (Indiana), 1971-1997 (Box 48, Folder 9-11, Box 49, Folder 1, Box 90, Box 98, Box 99)
    Correspondents include: Bill Whorall, LEVEL, Lucky Baby Retreat House.
  - United States (Iowa), 1985-1993 (Box 49, Folder 2, Box 87, Folder 5, Box 98, Box 104, Folder 8)
    Correspondents include: Drawing Legion (Photo STATIC-Copy Culture), Latin American Human Rights Advocacy Center, Mimi Holmes, Playboy, Portraits of Friends, Subspace, The Electric Bank.
  - United States (Kansas), 1981 (Box 49, Folder 3, Box 90)
    Correspondents include: Northern Kentucky University, SueZ Q, Transformar.
  - United States (Kentucky), 1985-1987 (Box 49, Folder 4, Binder 16, Box 99)
    Correspondents include: Todd Robert Machin
  - United States (Louisiana), 1991-2005 (Box 49, Folder 5, Box 83)
    Correspondents include: McNeese State University
  - United States (Maine), 1982-2005 (Box 49, Folder 6-8, Box 83, Folder 3, Box 84, Folder 5, Box 85, Folder 6-7, Box 86, Folder 3,8, Box 87, Box 88, Box 90, Box 94, Folder 12, Box 98, Box 99)
    Correspondents include: Bern Porter, Carlo Pittore, Dog Ear Press, Farrago, Franco Ballabeni, H.O.M.E Inc, Kristof Sebris, Luiza Brown, Mark Melnicove, Marta Africa, Natasha Mayeus and Mark Melnicove, Owen F. Smith, R. Martin, Reed Altemus, Spacecraft, U.M.U.A., Wafer Face.
  - United States (Maryland), 1981-2004 (Box 49, Folder 9-12, Box 83, Folder 9, Box 84, Folder 4-5, Binder 15, Binder 17, Box 88, Box 90, Box 98)
    Correspondents include: Burkely Hermann, D Hubbard, Eastern Short Arts, Mail Art Censorship Archive, Newark Press, Phillip S. Hensel, Project 7 (Maryann Crowe), Republique da Funlovia (Hal Tatelman), "REV." Paul, Sylvia, Tentatively, A Coincidence, Terry Cafield, Travis Little, Wendy Lanxner-Porter.
  - United States (Massachusetts), 1979-2006 (Box 49, Folder 13, Box 50, Folder 1-7, Box 84, Folder 4-6, Box 85, Folder 1,3,5, Box 86, Folder 1,3,6,7,8, Box 87, Folder 1,2,4, Binder 15, Binder 16, Box 88, Box 89, Box 90, Box 92, Folder 6, Box 93, Folder 5, Box 94, Folder 13-17, Box 98, Box 99)
    Correspondents include: Abuse, Alex Lippsich, Bernard Banville, Boston Film (Video Foundation), Brush Gallery, Carol Marnelakis, Crackerjack Kid, Danielle Fino, Don Milken, Eco Texture Inc., Ed Adamchek, Ellen Hatzakis, Emily Goodwin, Event Works (Jeremy Grainger), F. Cramer, Fidelity Investments, Florian Cramer, G.H. Kahl Co, Guillermo Cuellar, Helen C. Gouzounis, Jesse, John Marnelakis, L. Berube, Marsh and Mclennan Inc. ("JC"), Matthew Corcaron, Michael Schoenberg, Miss Mary, Mr. Fabulous, New England Art Therapy Institute, NNN, Patti Churri, Peter Mitchell, Recorded Security Video Productions, Resources (Richard Gardner), Richard F. Hay Sr., Robin Costa, S'Pool, Sarah Garden Armstrong, Sherry Steiner, Stangroom, Steven Random, The NBCs, Uncle Don, Viktor V, Wendy Sayshi, Xona (Exit Studios), Young Whippersnapper Press, Zona.
  - United States (Michigan), 1980-2004 (Box 50, Folder 8-9, Box 85, Folder 6, Box 86, Folder 4, Binder 15, Box 88, Box 89, Box 90, Box 98, Box 99, Box 104, Folder 9)
    Correspondents include: A Classic Pair, Agent Detroit, C. Schneek, Catherine Kakowska, Cerebral Shorts, Christian Herman, Cliff Berns, Comfort and Satisfy Bottom, Ed.F. Higgins, Lightworks, Marilyn Dammann, Marilyn Zimmerman, Neither/nor, Stamping Grounds, Thomas Edward Weston, Thomas Wiloch, University Microfilms International.
  - United States (Minnesota), 1983-1995 (Box 50, Folder 10, Box 70, Folder 1-2, Box 86, Folder 6, Box 87, Folder 2, Binder 17, Box 88, Box 90, Box 98, Box 99)
    Correspondents include: Art Police, Billy Curmano, Chris Lugo, Dan Unger, David M. Miller, De Siray Dodge, Gray (Potratz), Greet-O-Matie, Jerry Madson, Kiehle Gallery, Road Kill, Terresinka Pareira, Wirth.
  - United States (Missouri), 1981-1990 (Box 70, Folder 3-4, Binder 16, Box 88)
    Correspondents include: Carolyn Hassenfratz, Christian Herman, Dave Van Hee, Not Again Graphics.
  - United States (Montana), 1976-1980 (Box 70, Folder 5, Binder 16)
    Correspondents include: Recycled Reality Studios
  - United States (Nebraska), 1983-2003 (Box 70, Folder 6, Box 84, Folder 5, Binder 16)
    Correspondents include: Crackerjack Kid, Dazar Omahahaha, Muscular Dystrophy.
  - United States (Nevada), 1986-2006 (Box 70, Folder 7, Box 84, Folder 5, Box 87)
  - United States (New Hampshire), 1989 (Box 70, Folder 8, Binder 15)
    Correspondents include: Crackerjack Kid
  - United States (New Jersey), 1980-2005 (Box 70, Folder 9-11, Box 84, Folder 4-5, Box 85, Folder 5, Box 86, Folder 8, Box 87, Folder 2,5, Binder 15, Binder 16, Box 89, Box 90, Box 93, Folder 6, Box 95, Folder 9, Box 99, Box 100, Folder 4, Box 101, Item 2)
    Correspondents include: Action/Image, Alcorn Design Illustration, Andrew Seldenfeld, Bryan Harrison, Carolla von Hoffmanstahl, Coco Gordon, Colgate-Palmolive Co., Dan Morgan, Desmond Mclean, Dominic J. Uricella, Donald Muller, Doria-Assembling, Doug Spear, Dragonfly Dream, Emily Allon, Glynis, Half-Life Network Magazine, Hightstown High School, Jill Cliffer-Baratta, Joanne Echevarria Myers, Mark Sonnenfeld, No. 58, Patty Antonivk, PortFolio, Press Me Close (K.S. Ernst), Reed N. Tell, Rickett's Records, Rutgers University: Department of Visual Arts, Simon and Schuster, Vanguard International, Xochimoki.
  - United States (New Mexico), 1984-2004 (Box 71, Folder 1-2, Box 86, Folder 6, Box 89, Box 94, Folder 18, Box 98, Box 101, Item 5, Flat-file-folder 6 Left)
    Correspondents include: Migration, Emmigration, Immigration, Penitentiary of New Mexico: Department of Education; Dragonfly Dream.
  - United States (New York), 1979-2006 (Box 71, Folder 3-9, Box 72, Folder 1-8, Box 73, Folder 1-10, Box 74, Box 75, Box 76, Folder 1-7, Box 82, Folder 8, Box 83, Folder 2-5, Box 84, Folder 1,2,4,5,6, Box 85, Folder 1,3,5, Box 86, Box 87, Folder 2022-01-05T00:00:00+00:00, Binder 15, Binder 16, Binder 17, Box 88, Box 89, Box 90, Box 91, Box 92, Folder 7, Box 93, Box 94, Folder 19, Box 95, Folder 10, Box 96, Folder 6, Box 97, Folder 2022-05-06T00:00:00+00:00, Box 98, Box 99, Box 101, Item 4, Box 104, Folder 10-11)
    Correspondents include: 3rd Street Music School, 4-U-2 Post Magazine, A.J. Lazarus Associates, Inc., A.K. Lipton, Above Average Productions, Abrams/Brill, Aching Loins Publishing Company, Adam Tinkoff, Addante Design, Alan J. Miller, Alchemial Space, Alex Lippisch, Alexander Josef and Katherine Hirka, American Institute of Graphic Arts, Amy Scarola, Anita and Jay, Anna Hurwitz, Anne Troy, Arto Posto, Avenue B Art School, B. Barton, Barbie Denis, Barbwire, Bean Curd Bandit, Beth Bartholomew, Beth Gorrie, Bikini Girl Magazine, Bill Hermanini, Bill Paulauskas, Bill Roberts, Bob Z, Bob's X-ray Monistary, Bobby Smith, Bolté, Bonnie Stylides, Buchner and Harpsichords, Buddy Flip, C. Deenply, Cadwaller Wickersham, Caren Zwiefler, Carlo Pittore, Carsten Schmidt-Olsen, Catherine "Kitsy" Stine, César Olhguray, Charles Doria, Chester Kasowski, Chocolate Waters, Chris Cosma, Christopher Durang, Circle Arts, Inc., City University of New York (CUNY): Hunter College, Claire Dunyhy, Claudine Barbot, Coco Gordon, Craig Purcell, D. Whitehead, damien(ism) (The Gallery of Fine Tuning), Dave Van Hee Hee Hee, David Cole, David Hunter, Dean Quasi-No-Dough, Debbie Davies, Denise Schiera, Dick Shreve, Dixie Paper Co., Dream State Press, Duke Ellington, Echo Communications Group, Inc., Eileen Arnow-Levine, Emily Harvey, Eva Lake, Factsheet Five, FaGaGaGa, Fawn Burkun and Larry Sklaw, Felice Nittolo, Fernand Barbot, Flash Art, Francine Brooks, Freya Zabritsky, Fuller Institute, G.W. Hewlitt High School, Gallery XOXO, George Deem, Georgian Henelry (Red Spot), Gerard Barbot, Gil Tucker, Glynis Albert, Glynis Miller, Gorrie, Greenwitch Artist Supply, Gustav Häggland, Hans Braumüller, Hokey Mokey, International Society of Copier Artists, James Quinlan, Jan Henderikse, Janet Ziff, Jerry Kaplan, Jill Cliffer, Joachim Frank (ART?-COM ON!), Joan Shepard, Joel Cohen, John Barnard, John Evans, John Jonas, John M. Bennett, John Peter Zenger, Johnny B on the loose graphix, inc., Jones Very, Joseph Nechvatal, Judy Spak, Julie Hagan Bloch, Junior College of Albany, Katherine Clanmer, Kathleen Farrell, Kathy Caridi, L. S. Silver, Le Pientre NATO, Lena Mcnally, Liberation Book Club, Linda E. Ketchum, Lisa Baumgardner, Little Shiva (The Ministry of Fun), Long Fellow, Lor Faye Gillian, Lori Gilman, Louise M. Millmann, Luc Fierens, Lynda Buckley, Mackay Society (The Arrow Bulletin), Margaret Segall, Marilyn R. Rosenberg, Marilyn Rosenbery, Mark Corroto, Mark Rosenberg, Mark Russell, Matthew Bisceglia, Matthew Goldstein, Matty Jankowski, Melody Hope Stein, Michael Robert (Atelier Gallery), Mike Miskowski, Mina Jesberger, Minor Injury, Miracle Media, MU New York Records, Museum of the American Indian, New York Health and Racquet Club, New York University: Tisch School of Arts, Nick and Nora Charles, Nirvana Club One, No Business As Usual, ON the Media, Pall Waston, Pappas, Patricia Antoniuk, Patrick Symes, Paul Kuhrman, Paul Walton, Penelope Goodfriend, Performance Space 122, Pete Abrams, Pete Spence, Pop Smear, Printed Matter, Public Image, R.Knots, Radio Free Dada, Ragged Edge Press (The Sticker Dude), Randy Epley, Re FLUX Editions, Reid Wood, Reno, Richard F. Shepard, Richard Kostelanetz, Richard Plant, Rimma Gerlovina, Robert Delford Brown, Robert J. Barsch, Robert Risko, Robin Kahn, Rubber Stamp Madness, Rusell Hogan, Samuel Weiser Inc., Sarah Jackson, Seditious Delicious, Sheldon Silver, Social Justice Center of Albany, Inc.: Albany Peace and Energy Council, Sonnabend Gallery, Sound of Pig, Stephanie Gildersleeve, Steve Dalanchinsky, Susan Wides, Suzako Sato, Swan Song, Inc., Sylvia Sherry and Thomas David Little, T. Baum, Takashi Shimamoto, Tally Ross Johnson, Tamara Wyndham, Tandler Textile, Inc., Ted Mook and Wendy J. Ehrlich, TEHCHING HSIEH, The American Federation of Art, The Duplex Planet Magazine, The Network-Ers, The New York Times, The Village Voice (Joe Levy), Theater of Coincidence, Third Wave Enterprises, Time and Space Limited (Linda Mussmann), Tom Warren, Tomasz Sikorski, Truman Peyote, United Nations Mission, Unkown Products, Inc. (Joe Rosen-Echo), Victoria Kelly, Vincent Lawless, Ward-Nasse Gallery, William K. Dobbs.
  - United States (North Carolina), 1983-1995 (Box 76, Folder 8, Box 77, Folder 1, Box 87, Binder 15, Box 88, Box 89, Box 90, Box 98, Box 99)
    Correspondents include: American Biographical Institute, Don Morgan, Dr. Ken, Frank Thompson, Robert Saunders, Ruth Ava Lyons, Water/World, Weatherspoon Art Gallery.
  - United States (Ohio), 1979-2003 (Box 77, Folder 2-8, Box 78, Folder 1-10, Box 79, Folder 1-3, Box 83, Folder 6-7, Box 84, Folder 4, Box 85, Folder 2,5,6,7, Box 86, Folder 1,3, Box 87, Binder 15, Binder 16, Binder 17, Box 88, Box 89, Box 90, Box 91, Folder 9, Box 93, Folder 8, Box 94, Folder 20-22, Box 97, Folder 2022-07-08T00:00:00+00:00, Box 98, Box 99, Flat-file-folder 4 Right, Box 104, Folder 12)
    Correspondents include: Bob Schimel, Christine French, Dennis Miller, Eric Low, Frank Green, Jeff Reding, Jodi Bleiman, Joel Lipman, John M. Bennett, John Stickney, Kent May 4 Center, Kent State University: School of Speech Communication, Larry L. Snyder, Magda Cathay, Marylee Lewis, Mel and Mark Corroto, Michael Heaton, Ralph Metzer, SAIN⊥, State of Being, Steven B. Smith (mutant entradish III), The Spitter.
  - United States (Oklahoma), 1986 (Box 79, Folder 4, Box 90)
    Correspondents include: Boon Dance Baby Pants
  - United States (Oregon), 1984-1995 (Box 79, Folder 5-7, Box 83, Folder 5, Box 87, Box 88, Box 89, Box 98, Flat-file-folder 1 Right)
    Correspondents include: A Forest Gathering of Poets, Al Ackerman, Anna Guillemot, Dewey Ya Fools, Lilian A. Bell, Mark Rose, Performers and Artists for Nuclear Disarmament (The International Shadow Project), Peter Boners Unlimited.
  - United States (Pennsylvania), 1980-2006 (Box 79, Folder 8-10, Box 82, Folder 8, Box 86, Folder 1-2, Box 87, Folder 2-3, Box 88, Box 90, Box 98, Box 99)
    Correspondents include: Constant Cause, David Gerbstadt, DUCMANH AHA!, Information Sickness, Matt Wrbican, Maximum Traffic, Mengato Rippel, New Penn Press, Nexus, Official Shnn Mail Art, Stuart Horn, Thomas C. Waters, Tyler School of Arts (Jesse Baker), Wyeth-Ayerst International.
  - United States (Rhode Island), 1985-1988 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    Correspondents include: Dawn Zero Erickson, Dream Magazine, HOR.
  - United States (South Carolina), 1989 (Box 80, Folder 1, Box 88)
    Correspondents include: Lesta Sue Hardee, Monster Truck Cartoon Co. (Mark Blackwell).
  - United States (South Dakota), 1983-1986 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    Correspondents include: Don Boyd, "That's What I Like About The West" (International Correspondence Art Exhibition).
  - United States (Tennessee), 1984-2000 (Box 80, Folder 3, Binder 15, Box 90)
    Correspondents include: Bill Stegall (Full Court Press), East Tennessee State University: Department of Art, Hipslit Sass, Progressive Education, Slocumb Gallery.
  - United States (Texas), 1983-2005 (Box 80, Folder 4-9, Box 84, Folder 2, Box 86, Folder 1,6, Box 87, Folder 1, Binder 15, Binder 17, Box 88, Box 90, Box 94, Folder 23-25, Box 98, Box 99)